http://www.architecturemedia.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Our commitment
Architecture Media Pty Ltd has established this privacy policy in accordance with the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000, and has a firm commitment to respect your privacy accordingly. This privacy policy covers all personal information that we hold and any personal information that we may from time to time collect. This Privacy policy explains our undertaking not to pass on any of your details without your consent.
Collection and use of personal information
When we ask you to provide personal information we will do so in a lawful and fair way. Generally this information is collected to keep your registration with us up-to-date or to improve our services to you. It may also be collected when you request goods or information from us or from a third party who is collecting your information through us so that we or they can supply goods or information requested by you. The provision of the information is voluntary. However, if you choose not to provide the information requested we may be unable to keep you informed about products, services, offers and events or to process your request e.g. registration, purchase or enquiry, and this may preclude or limit your access to the goods and services available. We will tell you why we are collecting the information and who are the third parties to whom we may disclose that information. Information as to how and where to contact us will also be available. If we collect information from a third party we will take reasonable steps to advise you of that collection promptly.
Disclosure of information
We will only disclose personal information in accordance with the Act. This means that it will be disclosed if:
we told you when collecting it that it would be disclosed for that purpose or for a related purpose that you would reasonably expect;
we have your consent;
it is part of business assets which we are selling;
we are required by law to disclose it; or
it is otherwise permitted under the Act
Your choice
Direct marketing offers will contain an opportunity to opt out and a low cost way of contacting us if you do not wish to receive further marketing offers.
Quality of information
We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information that we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up to date.
Security
We are committed to protecting your privacy and will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information we collect is protected from loss and misuse and from unauthorised access, modification and disclosure.
Access to the information we hold
You can access your personal information upon request. However, there are occasions when this access may be denied under the exemptions contained in the Act.
Privacy Policy access
This policy is available upon request or from our web site www.architecturemedia.com. It may be reviewed and updated from time to time.
Privacy enquiries
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or any privacy related dealings with us, you can contact:Jacinta Reedy, General Manager OperationsArchitecture Media Pty LtdLevel 6, 163 Eastern RoadSouth Melbourne Victoria 3205AUSTRALIAPhone: +61 3 8699 1000Fax: +61 3 9696 2617Email: jacinta.reedy@archmedia.com.au
